Fatimah binti Abd Rahman No 1, Jalam Gamelan 11/2e, Seksyen 11, 40000 Shah Alam Selangor Darul Ehsan

## TO WHOM IT MAY CONCERN

Dear Sir/Madam,

# APPLICATION FOR A POST IN ACCOUNTING FIELD

I am Fatimah Bachelor (Hons) in Accounting graduate, from Universiti Utara Malaysia (UUM). My main purpose composing this letter is to request for job placement.

I believe my working experience for more than 3 years with previous employer will be of great value should I join your company. I have been exposed to the task and responsibility in the field of technical as well as management. I am confident that my working experience has vastly improved my knowledge, skill and competencies to be proficient accountant.

My strength and asset in which your company can leverage are:

WORKING EXPERIENCE	Exposed to account payable related duties and liaise with external and internal parties			
	AEGIS BPO MALAYSIA SDN BHD			
	Exposed to GL related duties and liaise with internal parties			
	Handling AR related duties			
MEMBERSHIP	MIA care member			
AFFILIATION				
SOFTWARE SKILLS	SAP in Fi			
	• UBS			
	BOSS Software			
	Microsoft Dynamic GP			
TOP LEADERSHIP	Secretary of Project "Kenali UUM"			
ACHIEVEMENT	<ul> <li>Learned to ascertain event held smoothly</li> </ul>			
	<ul> <li>Learned to organize a program for students</li> </ul>			
	Managed to handle 50 participant in this program			
	Bereau activity of "Pesta Pantun Timbalan Naib Canselor"			
	<ul> <li>Learned to arrange the program's activity</li> </ul>			

I should welcome an opportunity to discuss how can i fit into your esteem organization and contribute to its future growth. Should you have any inquiry, please contact me via phone (+6)0134330221 or email <a href="mailto:msfatimah.rahman@yahoo.com">msfatimah.rahman@yahoo.com</a>. Thank you for your time and consideration.

Yours sincerely,

## **FATIMAH ABD RAHMAN**

# FATIMAH BINTI ABD RAHMAN BACHELOR (HONS) IN ACCOUNTING

## PERSONAL INFORMATION

NRIC : 900215-05-5556

NATIONALITY : Malaysian LANGUAGE : Malay & English

SPONSOR : PTPTN

**CONTACTS** 

HP: (+60) 013-4330221

Email: msfatimah.rahman@yahoo.com

#### **PERMANENT ADDRESS**

No 1, Jalan Gamelan 11/2E,

Seksyen 11, 40000 Shah Alam Selangor Darul Ehsan



	EDUCATION BACKGROUND		E SKILLS
2007-2006	Dec 2013 - July 2009 Universiti Utara, Malaysia	Certified     Score: 8	d SAP in FI 34%
Teknik Tuank	· · ·	UBS     BOSS S	oftware
2009-2008 Pahang Matriculation, Malaysia			d Microsoft function
CGPA:3.47/4.	00		oft Dynamic GP

## **WORKING EXPERIENCE**

# **AEGIS BPO(MALAYSIA) SDN BHD**

Period : Nov 2015- current
Department : Finance Department
Position : Account Executive

- Prepare month end close journal entry and ensure journal is correct and posted in the system.
- To perform general accounting day-to-day transaction processing and ensuring delivery quality in term of accuracy, completeness and timeliness
- Update the fixed asset register. Ensure assets is capitalize and dispose as per policies
- Prepare monthly report that requested by HQ

### **GREEN PACKET BERHAD**

Period : Oct 2013- Oct 2015
Department : Finance Department
Position : Account Executive



- Verifying the trade and non-trade invoices by ensuring the details are properly accounted for before posted into the system
- Liaising with supplier and banker from all over the world when necessary
- Processing the staff claims on a monthly basis
- Monitor outstanding invoices payable, verifying statement of account, prepare payment voucher and payment
- Perform reconciliation of payable/vendor invoices and raise the dispute when necessary
- Work closely with the finance team within the organization for monthly closing schedule and ensures it is closed on a timely basis

### P.S. YAP, ISMA & ASSOCIATES

Period : 6 months (Internship)
Company : P.S.Yap, Isma & Associates

Department: Auditing, Accounting and Company Secretarial

- Handle company secretarial works such as name search, formation of companies, maintain statutory records.
  - Liaise with internal clients and external parties such as SSM, clients, and bank.
- Prepare full set of account for different type of industries
- Handle statutory audit, prepare audit reports and present on audit finding and recommendations



# **RELEVANT COURSES TAKEN**

- Accounting Theory and Practices
- Auditing and Assurance I
- Auditing and Assurance II
- Introduction to Financial Accounting
- Financial Accounting & Reporting I
- Financial Accounting & Reporting II
- Financial Accounting and Reporting III
- Financial Accounting and Reporting IV
- Specialized Taxation
- Forensic Accounting

- Public Sector Accounting
- Specialized Financial Accounting
- Company Secretarial Practices
- Management Accounting I
- Management Accounting II
- Advanced Management Accounting
- Information Technology in Accounting
- Accounting System Analysis and Design
- Principle of Taxation
- Advance Taxation

MY TOP LEADERSHIP EXPERIENCES			
MICPA Leadership Camp	<ul> <li>Position: Team leader of bureau publicity</li> <li>Responsible to supervise and coordinate all the advertisement activities</li> <li>Contributed toward s completion of the event</li> </ul>		
Annual General Meeting North Varsity Accounting Club (NOVAC) Accounting Day by NOVAC	Position: Team leader of bureau protocol     Responsible to prepare the text for emcee     Manage to organize the event smoothly     Position: Team leader of bureau activity     Responsible to lead and arrange the flow of event accordingly		

EXTRA CURRICULUM AND ACTIVITIES	ADJUNCT LECTURES BY UUM		
<ul> <li>Committee of CIMA, COB Accounting Day</li> </ul>	SPEAKER	TITLES	
<ul> <li>Committee of 'Jualan' Big Apple NOVAC</li> <li>Participant of DPP Mas Family Day 2011</li> </ul>	Tan Sri Dato Setia Hj Ambrin	Accounting-career path	
<ul><li>Active member of 'Cak Lempong' Club</li><li>Participant of Sambutan Maulidur Rasul 1432H</li></ul>	Bin Buang		

PERSONAL REFERENCES						
P.S Yap, Azlan Abas & Wong Manager of Company Secretarial Ms Zuliati Binti Ahmad	Aegis BPO Malaysia Sdn Bhd Assistant Manager Mr Mohd Fahmi	Nor Idham bin Che Ghani Manager, Career Advisory Services,				
Chartered Accountants, No. 89-2, Jalan 1/91, Taman Shamelin Perkasa, 56100 Cheras, Kuala Lumpur. Tel no: 03-9285 3313/ 016-659 5321 Email: ypkaudit@yahoo.com	Level 2, Symphony House Pusat Dagangan Dana 1 Jalan PJU/1A/46, 47301 PJ Selangor Darul Ehsan Tel no: 013-343 2606 Email: mohd.fahmi@aegisbpo.com.my	Bandar Seri Iskandar, 31750 Tronoh, Perak Phone: 016-592 9462 Email: noridhamcheghani@yahoo.com				



TO WHOM IT MAY CONCERN

Dear Sir/Mdm,

#### RECOMMENDATION LETTER

As a career advisor, I am writing this letter to strongly recommend Ms Fatimah to your firm.

2. Knowing her for that period, I described her as a disciplined, hardworking and conscientious person. She is very committed to her duties, a fast learner and very independent. Describing her accounting skill, I'd ensure you that she has the skills, attributes and qualities to become an excellent accountant. Therefore I believed that she had acquired skills to apply professional judgment.

I highly recommend her for employment. She is a team player and would make a great asset to any organization.

Thank you.

Yours sincerely,

NOR IDHAM BIN CHE GHANI

Career Advisor, Career Advisory Services, Universiti Teknologi PETRONAS, 31750 Tronoh Perak, Malaysia

idhamg@petronas.com.my/0165929462

## UNIVERSITI TEKNOLOGI PETRONAS

INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY PETRONAS SDN. BHD. (Company No: 352875U) Wholly-owned subsidiary of PETRONAS